Analyzing...

- Your file contains 31 prompt-completion pairs. In general, we recommend having at least a few hundred examples. We've found that performance tends to linearly increase for every doubling of the number of examples
- Your data does not contain a common separator at the end of your prompts. Having a separator string appended to the end of the prompt makes it clearer to the fine-tuned model where the completion should begin. See https://platform.openai.com/docs/guides/fine-tuning/preparing-your-dataset for more detail and examples. If you intend to do open-ended generation, then you should leave the prompts empty
- All completions start with prefix `{"intent": "get`. Most of the time you should only add the output data into the completion, without any prefix
- All completions end with suffix `"}}`
- The completion should start with a whitespace character (` `). This tends to produce better results due to the tokenization we use. See https://platform.openai.com/docs/guides/fine-tuning/preparing-your-dataset for more details

Based on the analysis we will perform the following actions:
- [Recommended] Add a suffix separator ` ->` to all prompts [Y/n]: Y
- [Recommended] Remove prefix `{"intent": "get` from all completions [Y/n]: Y
- [Recommended] Add a whitespace character to the beginning of the completion [Y/n]: Y


Your data will be written to a new JSONL file. Proceed [Y/n]: Y

Wrote modified file to `.\fine-tunning_prepared (1).jsonl`
Feel free to take a look!

Now use that file when fine-tuning:
> openai api fine_tunes.create -t ".\fine-tunning_prepared (1).jsonl"

After youÆve fine-tuned a model, remember that your prompt has to end with the indicator string ` ->` for the model to start generating completions, rather than continuing with the prompt. Make sure to include `stop=[""}}"]` so that the generated texts ends at the expected place.
Once your model starts training, it'll approximately take 2.87 minutes to train a `curie` model, and less for `ada` and `babbage`. Queue will approximately take half an hour per job ahead of you.
